[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Reports of poltergeist activity date back as far as ancient Roman times.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2004 film National Treasure, the lead character Ben Gates (Nicolas Cage) seeks the treasure for what purpose?", "correct_answer": "To clear his familys name and prove it does exist", "incorrect_answers": ["To solve the Lincoln conspiracy", "To get his family out of debt", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1903 Nobel Prize laureate  discovered radioactivity in 1896.", "correct_answer": "Henri Becquerel", "incorrect_answers": ["Wilhelm Conrad Rontgen", "Elihu Thomson", "Niels Bohr"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chris friend Brenda threatens to spike her stepmother\u2019s drink with what toxin in the comedy Adventures in Babysitting?", "correct_answer": "Drano", "incorrect_answers": ["Windex", "Pine Sol", "Clorox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These are people who do not eat anything that is derived from animals.", "correct_answer": "Vegans", "incorrect_answers": ["Lacto Vegetarians", "Demi-Vegetarians", "Fruitarians"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2000 Vin Diesel starred in this movie about marooned space travelers on a strange planet.", "correct_answer": "Pitch Black", "incorrect_answers": ["Riddick", "Doom", "Saturn 3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the hottest planet of the Solar System?", "correct_answer": "Venus", "incorrect_answers": ["Mars", "Mercury", "Uranus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Find the odd one.", "correct_answer": "Libra", "incorrect_answers": ["Taurus", "Capricorn", "Leo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the longest river located entirely within the territory of the state of California?", "correct_answer": "Sacramento River", "incorrect_answers": ["Mad River", "Salmon River", "Big River"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the father of Jem and Scout in the novel To Kill a Mockingbird?", "correct_answer": "Atticus Finch", "incorrect_answers": ["Harper Lee", "Bob Jones", "Boyd Smith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did the popular 80s movie Valley Girl premiere?", "correct_answer": "1983", "incorrect_answers": ["1981", "1984", "1982"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These 1990 movies were all nominated for the Razzie Award for Worst Picture. Which of them won?", "correct_answer": "The Adventures of Ford Fairlane", "incorrect_answers": ["The Bonfire of the Vanities", "Graffiti Bridge", "Rocky V"]}]